On this makeshift boat, some migrants will
have braved the ocean and its storms for
several days.
A small boat made with metal containers
and a tarp and an old engine.
Vessels this size and they'll be packed
with anywhere from two people to 20 people
aboard a vessel like this.
As you can see, there's not much room in
there.
They have bottles and bottles of water.
They never know how long they're going to
be out at sea.
The boat's passengers are all in the boat.
The dangers have probably been taken by
people smugglers off the coast of Miami.
It's a desperate attempt to make it to the
U.S.
by any means available to them.
The Coast Guard intercepted almost 5,000
migrants out at sea in 2015,
a figure which continues to increase.